startlocal.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy: Start Local - Your Local Indian Business Directory

You are here: [Home]() > Privacy Policy

## Privacy

**Introduction**   
Start Local Pty Ltd. respects each individual’s right to personal privacy.  We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement.  This statement applies solely to information collected at the Start Local Web site. ****

**Part I.   Information Collection**   
Start Local Pty Ltd collects information through our Web site at several points.  We collect the following information about primary visitors: Users Names, e-mail address and other personal information. 

We may also collect information which our users divulge about other people. Start Local Pty Ltd does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information. 

We collect this information through emails and contact forms.  The information is collected voluntarily. 

We may employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Start Local Pty Ltd to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users.  Our cookies may have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Start Local.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to Start Local and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Part II.   Information Usage.   
**The information collected by Start Local Pty Ltd will be used for providing users with information.  Users who provide information may receive list products, services, email announcements or advertisements. 

We offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours. 

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will update this notice. We have the right to change this notice at any time. 

**Part IV. Problem Resolution  
**If problems arise, users may contact Start Local Pty Ltd by using the [contact form provided](http://www.startlocal.in/contact.html).  We are committed to resolving disputes in the shortest time possible.

**Part V. Data Storage and Security  
** All staff of Start Local Pty Ltd are dedicated to upholding our privcy policy.
